A Guide to the Old Dominion University Photograph Collection 1930s-1990s
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- 1970s
  - Athletics-Sports Banquet (III), 1971 (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Athletics-Swimming (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Athletics-Swimming, Women's (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Athletics-Tennis (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Athletics-Track (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Athletics-Wrestling (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds (I) (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds (II) (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds (III) (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds (IV) (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Buildings and Grounds (V) (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Buildings and Grounds (VI) (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Buildings and Grounds (VII) (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Buildings and Grounds (VIII) (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Buildings and Grounds (IX) (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Buildings and Grounds (X) (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Buildings and Grounds (XI) (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Buildings and Grounds (XII) (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Academic Building (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds-New Administration Building (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Administration Building (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Arts and Letters Building (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Bookstore (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Chandler Hall (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Chemistry (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Child Study Center (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Computer Center (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Counseling Center (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Crittendon Hall (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Dormitories (I) (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Dormitories (II) (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Duckworth Hall (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Education (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Engineering (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Engineering Laboratory (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Fieldhouse (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Fine Arts (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Hughes Library (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Buildings and Grounds-New Library (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Life Sciences (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Mailroom (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Buildings and Grounds-The Mall (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Off Campus Student Housing (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Powhatan Apartments (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Buildings and Grounds-President's House (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Pretlow Planetarium (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Riverview (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Storm Damage (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Webb Center (I) (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Webb Center (II) (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Webb Center (III) (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Faculty, 34 Folders (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 10-Box 65, Folder 9:)
  - Faculty Activities (I) (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Activities (II) (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 19 Folders (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 12-Box 66, Folder 8:)
  - Musical Performances (I) (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Musical Performances (II) (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Musical Performances (III) (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Musical Performances (IV) (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Musical Performances-"The Adding Machine" (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Musical Performances-"By Appointment Only" (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Musical Performances-"Camelot" (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Musical Performances-"Friends of Distinction" (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Musical Performances-"New York Rock Ensemble" (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Musical Performances-"Oliver" (I) (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Musical Performances-"Oliver" (II) (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Musical Performances-"Roberta Peters" (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Musical Performances-"John Savory" (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Musical Performances-"Tod's Gal" (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Other Events (I) (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Other Events (II) (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Other Events-Arts Reunion (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Other Events-Azalea Festival (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Other Events-Berkley Clean-up (I) (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Other Events-Berkley Clean-up (II) (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Other Events-Career Fair (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Other Events-Cheerleading Clinic (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Other Events-Closing of "Red" Barrom's Shell Service Station, November 15, 1973 (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Other Events-College Bowl (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Duckworth Hall (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Education Building (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Fountain of Organized Labor (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Kaufman Mall (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Other Events-Earth Week (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Other Events-Explorer Olympics (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Other Events-Faculty-A-Fair (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Other Events-Fine Arts Festival (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Other Events-First Annual O.D.U School of Education Retreat (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Other Events-Frisbee Exposition/Tournament (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Other Events-Halloween Carnival (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Other Events-Halloween Haunted House (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Other Events-Inauguration of President Rollins: Color (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Other Events-Inauguration of President Rollins: Black and White (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Other Events-Inauguration of President Rollins: Interinstitutional Seminar (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Other Events-Interplay (I) (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Other Events-Interplay (II) (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Other Events-Interplay (III) (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Other Events-Interplay (Thea Musgrave Lectures) (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Other Events-Jazz Festival (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Other Events-Miss Amazon Contest (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Other Events-Miss Norfolk Contest (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Other Events-National Library Week, April 21-26, 1971 (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Other Events-NCAA Sports Clinic (I) (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Other Events-NCAA Sports Clinic (II) (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Other Events-Oriental Art Show (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Other Events-Parent's Day (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Other Events-ODU Police Auction (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Other Events-Salt II Debate (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Other Events-Save ODU Parade (I) (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Other Events-Save ODU Parade (II) (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Other Events-Skateboard Tournament, Spring, 1978 (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Other Events-Special Olympics (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Other Events-Tidewater Regional College Fair at Scope, 1977 (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Other Events-Town Meeting on Foreign Policy, 1978 (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Other Events-U.N. Day (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Other Events-Urban South Conference (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Other Events-V.A.S.G. Conference (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 19)
  - School of Business Administration (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 20)
  - School of Continuing Studies (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 21)
  - School of Education (I) (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 22)
  - School of Education (II) (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 23)
  - School of Engineering (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Student Life, 62 Folders (Box-folder Box 68, Folder 25-Box 71, Folder 10:)
  - Student Life-Blood Drive (I) (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Student Life-Blood Drive (II) (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Student Life-Gadfly (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Student Life-Mace and Crown (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Student Organizations (I) (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Student Organizations (II) (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Student Organizations (III) (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Student Organizations (IV) (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Student Organizations (V) (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Student Organizations (VI) (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Student Organizations (VII) (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Student Organizations (VIII) (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Student Organizations (IX) (Box-folder Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Student Organizations-Alpha Epslion Phi (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Student Organizations-Alpha Epslion Pi (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Student Organizations-Alpha Kappa Psi (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Student Organizations-Alpha Phi (I) (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Student Organizations-Alpha Phi (II) (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Student Organizations-Alpha Tau Omega (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Student Organizations-Alpha Xi Delta (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Student Organizations-American Society of Civil Engineers (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Student Organizations-Baptist Student Union (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Student Organizations-Biology Club (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Student Organizations-Campus Americans for Democratic Action (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Student Organizations-Canterbury House (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Student Organizations-Chi Omega (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Student Organizations-Circle K Club (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Student Organizations-Delta Phi Delta (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Student Organizations-Delta Phi Omega (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Student Organizations-Delta Sigma Lambda (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Student Organizations-Delta Sigma Phi (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Student Organizations-Delta Zeta (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Student Organizations-Forensics (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Student Organizations-Hillel Foundation (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Student Organizations-International Students Club (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Student Organizations-Kappa Alpha (I) (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Student Organizations-Kappa Alpha (II) (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Student Organizations-Lambda Chi Alpha (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Student Organizations-Marketing Club (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Student Organizations-Math Club (Box-folder Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Student Organizations-Newman Club (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Student Organizations-Omicron Delta Kappa (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Student Organizations-Phi Kappa Phi (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Student Organizations-Phi Kappa Tau (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Student Organizations-Phi Mu (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Student Organizations-Pi Beta Phi (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Student Organizations-Pi Kappa Alpha (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Student Organizations-Pi Kappa Phi (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Student Organizations-Pi Sigma Alpha (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Student Organizations-Radio Club (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Student Organizations-Sigma Nu (I) (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Student Organizations-Sigma Nu (II) (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Student Organizations-Sigma Phi Epsilon (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Student Organizations-Sociology Club (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Student Organizations-Student Government (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Student Organizations-Tau Beta Pi (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Student Organizations-Tau Kappa Epsilon (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Student Organizations-Theta Chi (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Student Organizations-Theta Xi (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Student Organizations-Veterans Association (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Student Organizations-Virginia College Council On Human Relation (O.D.C. Chapter) (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Student Organizations-Young Democrats Club (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Student Organizations-Young Republicans Club (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Student Portraits, 47 Folders (Box-folder Box 73, Folder 24-Box 75, Folder 19:)
  - Traditional Events (Box-folder Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Traditional Events-Annual Conference on Scottish Studies (Box-folder Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Traditional Events-Azalea Festival (Box-folder Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Traditional Events-Black History Month (Box-folder Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Traditional Events-Christmas Party for Underprivileged Children (Box-folder Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Traditional Events-Danceathon (Box-folder Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Traditional Events-Folk Festival (I) (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Traditional Events-Folk Festival (II) (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Traditional Events-Frustration Day (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (I) (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (II) (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (III) (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (I), 1970 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (II), 1970 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (I), 1971 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (II), 1971 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (III), 1971 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation, 1973 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation, 1975 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation, 1976 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation, 1977 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation, 1978 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation, 1979 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Traditional Events-Greek Week (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Traditional Events-Greek Week (I), 1971 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Traditional Events-Greek Week (II), 1971 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Traditional Events-Greek Week (III), 1971 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Traditional Events-Greek Week (IV), 1971 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Traditional Events-Greek Week (V), 1971 (Box-folder Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Traditional Events-Homecoming (I), 1970 (Box-folder Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Traditional Events-Homecoming (II), 1970 (Box-folder Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Traditional Events-Homecoming (III), 1970 (Box-folder Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Traditional Events-Homecoming (IV), 1970 (Box-folder Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Traditional Events-Homecoming, 1971 (Box-folder Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Traditional Events-Homecoming, 1975 (Box-folder Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Traditional Events-Homecoming, 1978 (Box-folder Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Traditional Events-Oyster Bowl (Box-folder Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Traditional Events-Phonathon (Box-folder Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Traditional Events-Preview (Box-folder Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Traditional Events-Women's Day (Box-folder Box 77, Folder 11)
  - University Administration, 21 Folders (Box-folder Box 77, Folder 12-Box 78, Folder 8:)
  - University Administration-Bugg, James (Box-folder Box 78, Folder 9)
  - University Administration-Rollins, Alfred (I) (Box-folder Box 78, Folder 10)
  - University Administration-Rollins, Alfred (II) (Box-folder Box 78, Folder 11)
  - University Administration-Rollins, Alfred (III) (Box-folder Box 78, Folder 12)
  - University Administration-Rollins, Alfred (IV) (Box-folder Box 78, Folder 13)
  - University Administration-Rollins, Alfred (V) (Box-folder Box 78, Folder 14)
  - University Administration-Webb, Lewis (Box-folder Box 78, Folder 15)
  - University Archives (Box-folder Box 78, Folder 16)
  - University Board of Visitors (Box-folder Box 78, Folder 17)
- Negatives
  - Negatives, 1950s (Box Box 79)
  - Negatives, 1950s (Box Box 80)
  - Negatives, 1958-1959 (Box Box 81)
  - Negatives, 1950s (Box Box 82)
  - Negatives, 1950s, 1970s, Glass Negatives 1900s (Box Box 83)
- Slides Relating to ODU History
  - Slides Relating to ODU History (Box Box 84)
- Transparencies and Postcards
  - Transparencies and Postcards; Stereo Transparencies; Postcards (Box Box 85)
- 1980s
  - Administration (Box-folder Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Aerials (Box-folder Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Alaska (Box-folder Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Alden's Dredging (Box-folder Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Alumni and Development (Box-folder Box 86, Folder 5)
  - APB (Box-folder Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Applied Marine Research Lab (AMRL) (Box-folder Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Archaeology (Box-folder Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Archives (Box-folder Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Art (Box-folder Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Arts Reunion (Box-folder Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Art Library (Box-folder Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Awards and Presentations (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Audiology (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Baby Lab (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Ballet (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Bands and Concerts (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Baseball Clinic (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Big Blue Beast (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Biology Department (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Black History Week (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Blood Drive (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Bookstore (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Business (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Cafeteria (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Campus Events (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Campus Ministry (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Campus Police (Box-folder Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Campus Police (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Chemistry (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Child Study Center (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Children (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Clown Workshop (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Community Services (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Community Unity Night (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Computer Science (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Concerts (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Construction (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Continuing Studies-Adult (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Continuing Studies-Children (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Continuing Studies-Folk Workshop (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Convocation (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Cross Walk (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Cultural Events and Convocation Committee (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Dental Hygiene (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Development (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Dismal Swamp (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Dorm Life (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Dormitories/Housing (Box-folder Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Ecological Science (Box-folder Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Education (Box-folder Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Engineering (I) (Box-folder Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Engineering (II) (Box-folder Box 89, Folder 4)
  - English (Box-folder Box 89, Folder 5)
  - English Language Center (Box-folder Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Every Women's Festival (Box-folder Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Exhibits (Box-folder Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Convocation (Box-folder Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Faculty, Staff, Unidentified (Box-folder Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Faculty (Box-folder Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Faculty-Engineering (Box-folder Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Faculty-Retired (Box-folder Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Folk Festival (Box-folder Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Films (Box-folder Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Founder's Day (Box-folder Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Field Hockey (Box-folder Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Films Produced on Campus (Box-folder Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Gendocon 1983 (Box-folder Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Gerontology (Box-folder Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Graduation/Commencement (I) (Box-folder Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Graduation/Commencement (II) (Box-folder Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Greeks-Fraternities and Sororities (Box-folder Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Grounds and Buildings (I) (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Grounds and Buildings (II) (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 2)
  - HACE (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Halloween (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Handicapped Awareness Day (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Health Center (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Health Fair (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Hellenic Conference (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 8)
  - History of ODU (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Homecoming (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Humanities (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Indoor Recreation (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Insurance Center (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 13)
  - International Programs-Jubilee (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 14)
  - International Programs-Model U.N. (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Intramurals (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Investment in Potential (Box-folder Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Jazz Festival (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Johns Hopkins Scholar, 1985 (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Karate/Judo (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Languages (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Lambert's Point (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Learning Resource Center (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Leisure Studies (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Library (I) (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Library (II) (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Library (III) (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Library/Hofheimer Art Library (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Literary Festival (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Madrigal Dinner (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Mail Room (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Main Street (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Management (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Marine Sciences (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Martin Luther King Day (Box-folder Box 92A, Folder 1)
  - Math (Box-folder Box 92A, Folder 2)
  - Media Center (Box-folder Box 92A, Folder 3)
  - Medical Technology (Box-folder Box 92A, Folder 4)
  - Midnight Brunch (Box-folder Box 92A, Folder 5)
  - Midrise (Box-folder Box 92A, Folder 6)
  - Minorities (Box-folder Box 92A, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 92A, Folder 8)
  - Monarchfest (Box-folder Box 92A, Folder 9)
  - Music (Box-folder Box 92A, Folder 10)
  - Norfolk and Newport News International Terminals (Box-folder Box 92A, Folder 11)
  - Nursing (Box-folder Box 92A, Folder 12)
  - Oceanography (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 1)
  - ODU Seal (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Off Campus-Downtown Norfolk (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Outdoor Recreation (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Performances (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Phonathon (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Physical Education (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Physical Plant (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Physics (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Political Rallies (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Powhatan (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Printing and Publications (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 12)